tmone.com.my 2018-03-04

# Privacy Statement

  Privacy Statement
  Dear TM ONE Customers,
  Thank you for your continuous support. As you are aware, Personal Data Protection Act 2010 (PDPA)
  that was passed in 2010 came into force on 15 November 2013. In our effort to ensure compliance to
  the said Act, we wish to draw your attention to TM ONE’S Privacy Notice as follows:
  What Personal Information Do We Collect?
  If you choose to transact with TM ONE i.e. for subscription of any products and / or services or use of
  TM ONE’S Portal, you will be asked to provide your personal information such as and may not be
  limited to name, identification card number, mailing address, phone number(s), email address(es),
  contact preferences. Where you intend to use TM ONE’S Portal for purposes of making transactions
  involving online payments, your credit card information may also be collected for the purpose of
  processing your payments.
  You will also be required to explicitly provide your consent to the provision of your personal
  information aforementioned in the form and manner as indicated in the registration process, failing
  which you will not be able to subscribe for the products and / or services or register for the use of our
  Portal.
  How We Use Your Personal Information?
  Your personal information will be used or processed for the following purposes:-
• assessing your application or continued provisioning of the products and / or services (whichever is
  applicable);
• finance operation including to verify and process payment, billing and billing enquiries;
• customizing advertisements and content on TM ONE’s website;
• responding to your enquiries;
• research purposes including historical and statistical purposes and analysis;
• general operation and maintenance of the products and / or services provided including audit and its related
  website(s);
• verification purposes;
• matching any data held by TM ONE or its group of companies relating to you from time to time;
• provide you with regular communications from TM ONE relating to the products and / or services
  provided; and
• investigation of complaints, suspected suspicious transactions and research for service or products
  improvement;
  By submitting your information to TM ONE, you hereby consent and authorize TM ONE to process
  and verify any information about you from any third party, especially credit bureau or credit reference
  agencies, which TM ONE may require in connection with your application for any of TM ONE’s
  products and/or services and/or review of the existing account with TM ONE. Such consent and
  authorization will extend to any information obtained from any of the account(s) presently maintained
  for you, any new application for any form of services rendered or products provided by TM ONE, such
  historical financial or credit records, data or information whether or not provided personally or by any
  other sources relating to you which was collected, received, captured, compiled, secured and/or
  obtained by TM ONE through or by whatever means or methods or forms.

  Disclosure of Your Personal Information
  If you choose to register and transact with TM ONE, your personal information may be shared where
  necessary and only on a need to know basis with other TM ONE subsidiary or agencies so as to
  serve you in the most efficient and effective manner. An example might be in terms of resolving or
  addressing complaints that require escalation to other TM ONE Subsidiary or agencies.
  TM ONE may disclose your personal information to the following parties for the purposes stated
  above:-
• TM ONE’s service providers or agents who are involved in providing the products and / or services;
• third parties (including those overseas) who provide data processing services;
• any credit reference agencies or, in the event of default, any debt collection agencies;
• any person, who is under a duty of confidentiality to which has undertaken to keep such data confidential,
  which TM ONE has engaged to fulfil its obligations to you; and
• any actual or proposed assignee, transferee, participant or sub-participant of TM ONE’s rights or business;
  Your personal information will not be disclosed to any unauthorized third party.
  Your personal information may be disclosed due to reasons of law, legal process, litigation, and/or
  requests from public and governmental authorities and any disclosure will be to such public and
  governmental authorities only. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that
  disclosure is necessary or appropriate for purposes of national security, law enforcement, or other
  issues of public importance.
  If you would like to request access or correction of your personal information or where you elect to
  limit TM ONE’s right to process your personal information, you may contact TM ONE personnel or call
  at +603 77128888. Any request of access to correct personal information may be subjected to a fee
  and also to applicable provisions in the PDPA. However, we reserve the right to decline requests
  which jeopardize the security and privacy of the personal information of others as well as requests
  which are impractical or not made in good faith.
  We may review and update this Privacy Notice from time to time to reflect changes in the law,
  changes in our business practices, procedures and structure, and the community’s changing privacy
  expectations. The latest version of the Privacy Notice will be made available at www.tmone.com.my
  In the event of any conflict between the English and other language versions, the English version
  shall prevail.
